You noticed last time, I tried to show you the importance
前回、私があなたに見せようとしたのは、その重要性でした。
of having gentleness
優しさを持つことの
because we have to work almost on a micro-crystalline field
なぜなら、私たちはほとんど微結晶のフィールドで作業しなければならないからです。
to have a contact, let's say, almost holistic, almost global on the body.
体全体に対して、ほとんどホリスティックな、全体的な接触を持つために。
So here, first information
だから、ここで、最初の情報です。
that I'm looking for to see if there's good expansion,
良い拡張があるかどうかを確認するために私が探しているのは、
it's the brain's tai chi.
それは脳の太極拳です。
So here, there's a bit of a lack behind.
だから、ここには少し不足があります。
That means she can get tired quickly already.
それは、彼女がすでにすぐに疲れてしまう可能性があることを意味します。
So that means we need to rebalance a mesenteric axis in Mademoiselle.
つまり、この女性の腸間膜軸のバランスを再調整する必要があるということです。
I can say it here, on the plane, on the axis
ここで言えるのは、平面上で、軸上で、
digestive,
消化器系の、
which is perhaps a little... it will help her.
それは少し...彼女を助けるでしょう。
We're going to revitalize her body a little.
私たちは彼女の体を少し活性化させます。
So here, I'm going to need to go...
だから、ここで、私は行く必要があります...
I don't have enough magnetic force.
磁力が足りません。
in the brain so I'm not pushed back enough and so I'm going to see if it's
脳の中に、だから私は十分に押し戻されていない、だから私は見に行くでしょう、それはどちらかです
already a
すでに
purely nutritional plan but you at the cream level there you go
純粋に栄養的な計画ですが、あなたはクリームのレベルで、ほら、
you relax your hands gently I'm going to
ゆっくりと手を緩めてください、私は
show you a little bit of what I see how you work so you are very precise
私が何を見ているか、あなたがどのように働いているかを少しお見せします。あなたは非常に正確です。
but you are too precise you
しかし、あなたは正確すぎます。あなたは
must dare to take some distance so
少し距離を取ることを敢えてしなければなりません。
And also a peripheral vision.
そして、周辺視野も。
Now, you let what's in your hand come.
さあ、あなたの手の中にあるものを受け入れてください。
You feel that we are not expanded enough.
十分に拡張されていないと感じます。
The first movement is an expansion.
最初の動きは拡張です。
I must have this feeling of expansion.
この拡張感を持たなければなりません。
Here, I'm going to see if, by modifying here, simply an axis,
ここで、私がここで、単に軸を変更することで、
except that I have to search very precisely for the mesenteric axis.
ただし、腸間膜軸を非常に正確に探し出す必要があります。
So I put myself, in a certain way, on an embryonic remnant.
だから、私はある意味、胚の残骸の上に身を置きます。
to see if I can help a little
少しでも助けられるかどうかを見るために
this force.
この力を。
There, I have to go look for it.
そこでは、探し出さなければなりません。
Tell me if there's a change
何か変化があれば教えてください。
in the...
その中で...
I have to look for the globality.
全体性を探さなければなりません。
For now, that's just a level
今のところ、それは単なるレベルです。
The omnispheres are searching.
全方位が探しています。
So, there, I...
だから、ここで、私は...
connect with an ancient vital energy, if you will, that the
もしあなたが望むなら、体が知っている古代の生命エネルギーとつながる
body knows, that the brain
体が知っている、脳が知っている
it used. And it's simply on a vascular plane
それは使われた。そしてそれは単に血管レベルでのことであり、
which is first an electrical field.
それはまず電気的な場である。
he just made an oxidative change
彼は酸化的な変化を起こしたばかりだ
he just changed his breathing
彼は呼吸を変えたばかりだ
I'm going to change, I'm going to put it
私は変える、私はそれを置く
on another level
別のレベルで
I'm going to put it on a plane
私はそれを平面に置く
another axis
別の軸
it's an axis
それは軸だ
a vestige
名残
almost phallomesenteric
ほとんど陰茎間膜の
if you will
もしあなたが望むなら
It's deeper in the brain.
それは脳のより深いところにある。
It's a deeper sensation in the brain.
それは脳のより深い感覚だ。
There, we're going to look for another level.
そこで、私たちは別のレベルを探求する。
You note the changes.
あなたは変化に気づく。
Watch what's going to happen.
何が起こるか見てみよう。
What do you feel?
何を感じる？
It goes back deep.
それは深みに戻っていく。
There, really, it's a good fact.
そこでは、本当に、それは良い事実だ。
and from the depth of the brain
そして脳の深さから
4 nutritional levels
4つの栄養レベル
what are the 4 levels
4つのレベルとは何か
4 pipes
4つの管
by vertebral artery
椎骨動脈
and carotid
そして頸動脈
we formed the basilar trunk
脳底動脈を形成した
there you go
ほら
I'm just going to
私はただ
it's on the back moment
それは後ろの瞬間にある
there you go so here
ほら、だからここ
we can already say that on
私たちはすでに言うことができる
it will release here
それはここを解放するだろう
we're going to release a plane for her
私たちは彼に平面を解放するだろう
watch what's going to happen
何が起こるか見てみよう
I'm going to release her
私は彼を解放するだろう
it's going to get hot in the head a bit
頭が少し熱くなるだろう
is that okay for you?
大丈夫ですか？
you'll see what happens
何が起こるか見てみましょう
and there we are on a subtle level
そして、私たちは微妙なレベルにいます
there you go that's
そうです、それは
how I work
私が働く方法です
there I'm in cellular
私は細胞レベルにいます
I'm in glial
私はグリア細胞にいます
yeah deep
ええ、深いところに
I'm going to release a level
私はあるレベルを解放します
you say a word that comes to me, should I say it or what?
私に浮かんだ言葉を言いますか？
truth. There you go, that will do you good, young lady, madam.
真実。さあ、それはあなたに良いでしょう、お嬢さん、奥様。
Diaphragm here which is a bit disturbed.
ここにある横隔膜が少し乱れています。
First diaphragm. There you go, you see, describe a bit your
最初の横隔膜。さあ、あなたの感じたことを少し説明してください。
feeling? Yes, it shocks a lot and then I felt it untie,
感じましたか？はい、とても衝撃的で、特にここがほぐれるのを感じました。
especially here.
特にここが。
And also a sensation in the mouth. The tongue and
そして、口の中にも感覚がありました。舌と
the heart bud. There you go,
心の芽。さあ、
that
それは
will revitalize your closed circuits a bit, that will do you good. Someone
あなたの閉じた回路を少し活性化させます、それはあなたに良いでしょう。誰か